const questions = [
    {
        _id: "1",
        question: "あ",
        category: {main: "hiragana", sub:'aiueo'},
        answers: ["a", "i", "u", "e"],
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        _id: "2",
        question: "い",
        category: {main: "hiragana", sub:'aiueo'},
        answers: ["a", "i", "u", "o"],
        correct: "i",
    },
    {
        _id: "3",
        question: "う",
        category: {main: "hiragana", sub:'aiueo'},
        answers: ["a", "o", "u", "e"],
        correct: "u",
    },
    {
        _id: "4",
        question: "え",
        category: {main: "hiragana", sub:'aiueo'},
        answers: ["a", "i", "u", "e"],
        correct: "e",
    },
    {
        _id: "5",
        question: "お",
        category: {main: "hiragana", sub:'aiueo'},
        answers: ["a", "o", "u", "e"],
        correct: "o",
    },
    {
        _id: "6",
        question: "か",
        category: {main: "hiragana", sub:'kakikukeko'},
        answers: ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke"],
        correct: "ka",
    },
    {
        _id: "7",
        question: "き",
        category: {main: "hiragana", sub:'kakikukeko'},
        answers: ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ko"],
        correct: "ki",
    },
    {
        _id: "8",
        question: "く",
        category: {main: "hiragana", sub:'kakikukeko'},
        answers: ["ka", "ko", "ku", "ke"],
        correct: "ku",
    },
    {
        _id: "9",
        question: "け",
        category: {main: "hiragana", sub:'kakikukeko'},
        answers: ["ka", "ki", "ku", "ke"],
        correct: "ke",
    },
    {
        _id: "10",
        question: "こ",
        category: {main: "hiragana", sub:'kakikukeko'},
        answers: ["ka", "ko", "ku", "ke"],
        correct: "ko",
    },
    {
        _id: "1",
        question: "ア",
        category: {main: "katakana", sub:'aiueo'},
        answers: ["a", "i", "u", "e"],
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        _id: "2",
        question: "イ",
        category: {main: "katakana", sub:'aiueo'},
        answers: ["a", "i", "u", "e"],
        correct: "i",
    },
    {
        _id: "1",
        question: "はしる",
        category: {main: "verb", sub:"life"},
        answers: ["run", "eat", "walk", "sleep"],
        correct: "run",
    },
    {
        _id: "2",
        question: "たべる",
        category: {main: "verb", sub:"life"},
        answers: ["run", "eat", "walk", "sleep"],
        correct: "eat",
    },
    {
        _id: "1",
        question: "ねこ",
        category: {main: "vocabulary", sub:"animal"},
        answers: ["dog", "fish", "cat", "bird"],
        correct: "cat",
    },
    {
        _id: "2",
        question: "いぬ",
        category: {main: "vocabulary", sub:"animal"},
        answers: ["dog", "fish", "cat", "bird"],
        correct: "dog",
    },
  ];
  
  module.exports = questions;